{"data":[{"question":"Ice ___ into water when its temperature rises beyond 0","a":"becomes","b":"turns","c":"goes","d":"gets","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Become: to begin to be something, or to develop in a particular way","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The leader is ___his teammates ready now.","a":"taking","b":"having","c":"doing","d":"getting","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Get ready: used to tell people to start a race","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The boss will ___ someone else to do it instead of you.","a":"have","b":"get","c":"make","d":"let","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Get someone to do sth: This construction usually means \"to convince to do something\" or \"to trick someone into doing something.\"","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"I have ___ you my best friend forever.","a":"trusted","b":"regarded","c":"considered","d":"hoped","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Consider: to think of someone or something in a particular way or to have a particular opinion","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Many non-English speaking people could not ___ the word thirty from the word dirty.","a":"talk about","b":"say","c":"tell","d":"speak of","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tell: to be able to see how one person or thing is different from another","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The minister has done something wrong; she is ready to ___ an apology.","a":"take","b":"make","c":"say","d":"do","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Make an apology ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Our school playground ___ an area of 1,500 square meters.","a":"is covered","b":"covers","c":"is extended","d":"extends","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Cover: to spread over an area","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"This house ___ cool in summer and warm in winter.","a":"is felt","b":"is being felt","c":"has been felt","d":"feels","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple present tense (express a general fact) + active voice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"These bananas look ___.","a":"nice","b":"nicely","c":"sweetly","d":"well","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Look\/taste\/smell nice:pleasant, attractive, or enjoyable","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The lady with glasses ___ a teacher.","a":"were liked","b":"looked","c":"looked like","d":"were like","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Look\/sound\/feel\/taste\/seem like: similar to something else, or happening in the same way","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"74","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"}]}